Guide to the Records of the Public History Program RG.20.9
New York University Archives
- Series VI: Media, 122563
  - 1994-1999, 138627
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, slides, 'From Neighbors to Clients?', cuid3479; 162721 (Box 10, Object 4)
    - Henry Street Settlement Workshop, 1993, slides, 'The Drama of Henry Street', cuid3480; 162722 (Box 10, Object 5)
    - "Everyone Knows It's Slinky," documentary, 1994, cuid3481; 134558 (Box 10, Object 6)
    - Steven Brier presentation, 'What Is Public History?,' 3/28/1995, Copy 1, cuid425; 134510 (Box 10, Cassette 7, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid425)
      Format: Hi8mm, Duration: 63 min.
      An attached note states that this cassette is dated 3/28/1994, though the label on the actual tape claims 3/28/1995. The processing of this item will align with the date on the cassette itself (1995), though it should be noted that this discrepancy exists.
    - Steven Brier presentation, 'What is Public History?,' 3/28/1995, Copy 2, cuid3482; 134539 (Box 10, Object 8)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Rehearsal, Tape 1, 1996; cuid3483; 134521 (Box 10, Object 9)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Rehearsal, Tape 2, cuid3484; 134446 (Box 10, Object 10)
      On this cassette is a skit arranged for this workshop, entitled: Easter with Matzos and Bintel Brief, The Bowery.
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Introductory presentations, 4/30/95, cuid426; 134433 (Box 10, Cassette 11, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid426)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Introductory Presentations, cuid3485; 122639 (Box 10, Object 12)
    - 'An Immigrant Mother' documentary, Lower East Side Workshop, 1995, cuid427; 134437 (Box 10, Cassette 13, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid427)
      This cassette was likely used for the 1995 Public History Workshop, which focused on life in the Lower East Side neighborhood.
      Format: Hi8mm, Duration: 11 min.
    - 'Easter with Matzohs: The Bowery' documentary, Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Copy 1, cuid428; 134431 (Box 10, Cassette 14, Box Digitized Access Files, File cuid428)
      It can be hypothesized that this item was used for the 1995 Public History Workshop, which focused on life in the Lower East Side.
      Format: Hi8mm, Duration: 46 min.
    - 'Easter with Matzohs: The Bowery' documentary, Tenement Museum Workshop, 1995, Copy 2, cuid3486; 134441 (Box 10, Object 15)
      It can be hypothesized that this cassette was used in conjunction with the 1995 Public History Workshop, which focused on immigrant life in the Lower East Side neighborhood.
    - Leon Birns Interview #1, by Ellen Noonan and John Spencer, 10/16/95, 1995; cuid3487; 134445 (Box 10, Object 16)
      Sony, Hi-8 Video Cassette, P6-60HMPX
      It can be assumed that this oral history interview was used in conjunction with the 1995 Public History Workshop, which focused on immigrant life in the Lower East Side neighborhood.
    - Leon Birns interview #2, 10/16/1995, cuid3488; 134438 (Box 10, Object 17)
      Attached note to cassette
      There was a note attached to the cassette that reads: 'this tape already dumped; see 3/4 to right side of machine'.
    - Leon Birns interview #2, 10/24/1995, by C. Turek and M. Menechella, cuid3489; 134436 (Box 10, Object 18)
    - Leon Birns Interview, Master Edit, 10/30/1995, cuid3490; 122626 (Box 10, Object 19)
      Tape characteristics
      This tape contains an edited interview. It does not rewind easily and delivers a loud, high-pitched sound.
    - Lower East Side location shots and Leon Birns Interview, 10/24/1995, cuid3491; 134495 (Box 10, Object 20)
      Related Event/Material
      It can be assumed that this cassette's material is related to the 1996 Public History Workshop, which focused on the history of the Lower East Side, particularly the Seward Park area.
      The interview with Leon Birns took place at Seward Park High School on the Lower East Side, a partner with the program for the 1996 Public History Workshop. The student interviewers were C. Turek and M. Manecella.
      Hi-8 Fuji E6-60 Video Cassette
    - Video Workshop Still Shots for Leon Birns project, 10/26/1995, by Finkelstein, Spencer, Noonan, cuid3492; 134505 (Box 10, Object 21)
      Supertape HG-150 Video Cassette
    - Susan DeMark Presentation, Video Workshop, 1995, cuid3493; 122627 (Box 10, Object 22)
    - 'Secrets of Washington Square,' Early Copy, Video Workshop, 1995, cuid3494; 122631 (Box 10, Object 23)
    - 'Secrets of Washington Square,' Final Edit, Video Workshop, 1995, cuid3495; 122630 (Box 10, Object 24)
    - Source Footage for 'Crowds, Gangs, and Cops' and Music for 'Zelig-Zulu'; projects by Rebecca Epstein and Rachel Mattson, 1995, cuid3496; 122629 (Box 10, Object 25)
    - Raw Footage, by Karl and Ellen, 1996, Dub Tape #1, cuid3497; 122570 (Box 10, Object 26)
    - Raw Footage, by Karl and Ellen, 1996, Dub Tape #2, cuid3498; 122566 (Box 10, Object 27)
    - Raw Footage, by Karl and Ellen, 1996, Dub Tape #3, cuid3499; 122567 (Box 10, Object 28)
    - Raw Footage, by Karl and Ellen, 1996, Dub Tape #4, cuid3500; 122568 (Box 10, Object 29)
    - Video Cassette, Karl & Ellen Stills, 1996; cuid3501; 134512 (Box 10, Object 30)
      Sony Hi-8 Metal-P Video Cassette
    - Paul Erasmus, Tape 3 (Jonathan Kovel Show Reel), 1996; cuid3502; 170790 (Box 18, Object 4)
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227586-0
    - 'Train Ride to Cape Town', Paul Erasmus, Tape 4 (first half), 1996; cuid3503; 170791 (Box 18, Object 5)
    - Paul Erasmus, Tape 4 (cont.), 1996; cuid3504; 170792 (Box 18, Object 6)
    - Paul Erasmus, Tape 5, 1996; cuid3505; 170793 (Box 18, Object 7)
    - 'Map of Africa', Paul Erasmus, Tape 7A, 1996; cuid3506; 170794 (Box 18, Object 8)
    - 'Photos, etc.', Paul Erasmus, Tape 8, 1996; cuid3507; 170795 (Box 18, Object 9)
    - Bob and Diana Mattson Interview, 4/1996, by Rachel Mattson, cuid3508; 122602 (Box 11, Object 1)
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227310-5
    - Archival Footage and Stills, Tape 1, 4/1996, by Rachel Mattson, cuid3509; 122632 (Box 11, Object 2)
    - Archival Footage and Stills, Tape 2, 4/1996, by Rachel Mattson, cuid3510; 122633 (Box 11, Object 3)
    - Archival Footage and Stills, Tape 3, 4/1996, by Rachel Mattson, cuid3511; 122634 (Box 11, Object 4)
    - Archival Footage and Stills, Tape 4, 4/1996, by Rachel Mattson, cuid3512; 122635 (Box 11, Object 5)
    - El Barrio y Loisaida Workshop, 1997, Tape 1, cuid3513; 122650 (Box 11, Object 6)
    - El Barrio y Loisaida Workshop, 1997, Tape 2, cuid3514; 122651 (Box 11, Object 7)
    - El Barrio y Loisaida Workshop, 1997, Tape 1, cuid3515; 122689 (Box 11, Object 8)
    - El Barrio y Loisaida Workshop, 1997, Tape 2, cuid3516; 122690 (Box 11, Object 9)
    - El Barrio y Loisaida Workshop, 1997, 'Immigrant Testimonies' portion, Tape 1, cuid3517; 122644 (Box 11, Object 10)
    - El Barrio y Loisaida Workshop, 1997, 'Immigrant Testimonies' portion, Tape 2, cuid3518; 122645 (Box 11, Object 11)
    - El Barrio y Loisaida Workshop, 1997, 'Immigrant Testimonies' and Sitcom portions, cuid3519; 122696 (Box 11, Object 12)
    - El Barrio y Loisaida Workshop, 1997, Tape 1, cuid3520; 134440 (Box 11, Object 13)
    - Liz Sevcenko at Charas, 4/25/1997, demo, cuid3521; 134518 (Box 11, Object 14)
      3M Hi-8 P6-60HXP, Audio Cassette
    - Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, Tape #1, cuid3522; 122688 (Box 11, Object 15)
    - Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, Master copy, cuid3523; 122686 (Box 11, Object 16)
    - Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, User copy, cuid3524; 122687 (Box 11, Object 17)
    - Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, Tape 1, cuid3525; 134461 (Box 11, Object 18)
      Hi-8 Video Cassette
    - Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, Tape 2, cuid3526; 134462 (Box 11, Object 19)
    - Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, Tape 3, cuid3527; 134469 (Box 11, Object 20)
    - Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, Drama Section only (Copy 1), cuid3528; 122683 (Box 11, Object 21)
    - Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, Drama Section only (Copy 2), cuid3529; 122684 (Box 11, Object 22)
    - Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, Drama Section only (Copy 3), cuid3530; 122685 (Box 11, Object 23)
    - 'Growing Up NYC Nisei During WWII,' Daniel Inouye's presentation, Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, cuid3531; 122648 (Box 11, Object 24)
      Student Work
      This documentary was completed by student Daniel Inouye.
    - New York Labor History Association Panel, Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, Tape 1, cuid3532; 122652 (Box 11, Object 25)
    - New York Labor History Association Panel, Activism in NYC Workshop, 1999, Tape 2, cuid3533; 134411 (Box 11, Object 26)
      Fuji E6-60 Hi-8 Video Cassette
    - Charas/El Boltio Footage, Liz Sevcenko, 3/22/1997, Tape 1, cuid3534; 122582 (Box 11, Object 27)
    - Charas/El Boltio Footage, Liz Sevcenko, 3/22/1997, Tape 2, cuid3535; 122575 (Box 11, Object 28)
    - Charas/El Boltio Footage, Liz Sevcenko, 3/22/1997, Tape 3, cuid3536; 122576 (Box 11, Object 29)
    - P.S. 122, Liz Sevcenko, 4/6/1997, Tape 1, cuid3537; 122577 (Box 12, Object 1)
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227311-3
    - P.S. 122, Liz Sevcenko, 4/6/1997, Tape 2, cuid3538; 122581 (Box 12, Object 2)
    - Yuri Kochiyama Interview, 3/21/1999, Part 1, cuid3539; 122594 (Box 12, Object 3)
    - Yuri Kochiyama Interview, 3/21/1999, Part 2; George Yuzawa Interview, 2/28/1999, Part 2, cuid3540; 122595 (Box 12, Object 4)
    - George Nagamatsu Interview, 4/2/1999, Part 1, cuid3541; 122598 (Box 12, Object 5)
    - George Nagamatsu Interview, 4/2/1999, Part 2, cuid3542; 122599 (Box 12, Object 6)
    - George Nagamatsu Interview, 4/2/1999, Part 3, cuid3543; 122600 (Box 12, Object 7)
    - George Yuzawa Interview Excerpts, 1999; Visuals #2, cuid3544; 122596 (Box 12, Object 8)
    - Fujio Saito Interview, 3/14/1999, cuid3545; 122601 (Box 12, Object 9)
    - Fujio Saito Interview Excerpts, 1999, cuid3546; 122588 (Box 12, Object 10)
    - 'NY - The Way it Was,' March 1994, cuid3547; 170257 (Box 16, Object 10)
    - Oral History class interview with Rose Down for Lower East Side Oral History Project, 3/24/1994, cuid3548; 170258 (Box 16, Object 11)
    - 'River of Steel: The Building of the New York City Subway,' Kerry Michaels and Stuart Math, Steel River Productions Inc., 1994, cuid3549; 170259 (Box 16, Object 12)
      Two personalized notes to Paul Mattingly dated January 23, 2002 and signed by Stuart Math accompany the VHS Cassette Tape
    - 'Signal to Noise: Life With Television, Show One: Watching TV Watching Us,' Cara Mertes, 1995, cuid3550; 170260 (Box 16, Object 13)
    - 'Signal to Noise: Life With Television, Show Two: TV Reality,' Cara Mertes, 1995, cuid3551; 170261 (Box 16, Object 14)
    - 'Signal to Noise: Life With Television, Show Three: Remote Control,' Cara Mertes, 1995, cuid3552; 170262 (Box 16, Object 15)
    - 'Bernice Abbott - Photographer,' PBS, 2/16/1995, cuid3553; 170263 (Box 16, Object 16)
    - 'Shaker Heights: The Struffle for Integration,' Stuart Math Films, 1998, cuid3554; 170264 (Box 16, Object 17)
    - 'Margaret Sanger', PBS, 10/15/1998, cuid3555; 170265 (Box 16, Object 18)
    - 'Frank Lloyd Wright, Part I,' PBS, 11/10/1998, cuid3556; 170266 (Box 16, Object 19)
    - 'Frank Lloyd Wright, Part II,' PBS, 11/11/1998, cuid3557; 170267 (Box 16, Object 20)
    - 'Midwife's Tale,' PBS, 1998, cuid3558; 170227 (Box 16, Object 21)
  - 2000-2007, 138629
    - 'Newark' documentary, by Mariel P. Isaacson, 1/2005, cuid3559; 122692 (Box 15, Object 2)
      U-matic: 3/4 in. analog, 2 VHS Cassette Tapes
    - Hudson Square Workshop, 2007, Part 1, cuid3560; 134528 (Box 15, Object 3)
      Verbatim DVD
    - Hudson Square Workshop, 2007, Part 2, cuid3561; 134529 (Box 15, Object 4)
      Maxell DVD-R
    - ITP/Public History Project: 'Someday…', cuid3562; 163515 (Box 15, Object 5)
    - Interview with David Hicks on the NYU History Department, 5/11/2000, cuid3563; 170268 (Box 15, Object 6)
      Hi-8 Video Cassette, SONY P6-60HMPX
    - Interview with Carl Prince on the NYU History Department, 10/24/2000, cuid3564; 170269 (Box 15, Object 7)
    - 'Barely Legal: Visions of the Past, Voices of the Future,' Brian W. Beaton, Spring 2001, Public History Project, cuid3565; 170239 (Box 15, Object 8)
      The VHS cassette tape is in a Quantegy VHS cardboard case. The cassette does not have a label and the only mark on the cardboard case is the number '61977' written on yellow tape.
    - 'The African Burial Ground: Whose History Is It?", Courtney Dralwer, October 2002, cuid3566; 170224 (Box 15, Object 9)
      General
      The tape is labeled "Courtney Brouwer 2-min spot"
    - 'Thunder in Guyana,' Suzanne Wasserman, 2002, cuid3567; 170270 (Box 16, Object 22)
    - 'Isabel Bishop: A Window on Union Square,' Sara Nolan, 10/29/2002, cuid3568; 170271 (Box 16, Object 23)
    - 'Post Industrial Visions of Steel,' Mariel P. Isaacson, Public History Seminar 2, Spring 2003, cuid3569; 170272 (Box 16, Object 24)
    - 'Coney Culture,' E.A. Durden, 5/9/2003, cuid3570; 170273 (Box 16, Object 25)
      Apple DVD-R
    - 'Grand Central: A Triumphant Portal,' Stephanie M. Carter, 5/12/2003, cuid3571; 170274 (Box 16, Object 26)
      Memorex DVD-R
    - 'Politicians and Popular Culture,' Rebecca Martin, Material Culture of American Life, 5/12/2003, cuid3572; 170275 (Box 16, Object 27)
      VHS Cassette Tape T-60PR
    - 'An Un-Gentlemanly Agreement: The Bates 7 and NYU,' Evan Friss and Joseph Felice, 5/2004, cuid3573; 170276 (Box 16, Object 28)
    - 'Networks of Transport, Networks of Influence: Alfred Ely Beach's Pneumatic Subway,' Terri Lonier, Fall 2004, cuid3574; 170277 (Box 16, Object 29)
    - 'Deindustrialization and Recovery,' Mariel P. Isaacson, 10/26/2004, cuid3575; 170278 (Box 16, Object 30)
    - 'It's All Business in Gay Times Square,' Anne Parsons, Public History Scenario, Oct. 2004, cuid3576; 170772 (Box 16, Object 31)
    - Public History Workshop, Tape 1, 5/3/05, 2005; cuid3577; 170770 (Box 16, Object 32)
      Panasonic Mini DV 60 SP / 90 LP videocassette
    - Public History Workshop, Tape 2, 5/3/05, 2005; cuid3578; 170771 (Box 16, Object 33)
      Panasonic Mini DV 60 SP / 90 LP Videocassette
    - 'Steeltown Hometown,' Mariel P. Isaacson, MPIFILMS, Ltd., 2005, cuid3579; 170279 (Box 16, Object 34)
      DVD
    - 'Creating Community in Greenwich Village,' Jenny Pachucki, Fall 2005, cuid3580; 170280 (Box 16, Object 35)
      Memorex DVD-RW
    - 'Lincoln Square to Lincoln Center,' Mariel P. Isaacson, Material Culture of American Life, Fall 2005, cuid3581; 170281 (Box 16, Object 36)
      Four (4) DVD-R
    - 'The Badlands of Manhattan?, 1 of 1,' Emily Levine, Fall 2005, cuid3582; 170242 (Box 16, Object 37)
      HP DVD-R 8X
    - 'La Quinta,' Maria Slena Howard, Material Culture of America, 12/13/2005, cuid3583; 170282 (Box 16, Object 38)
      TDK DVD-R 16X
    - 'The Road to Here...', Shira Rappaport, 12/2005, cuid3584; 170283 (Box 16, Object 39)
      DVD-R
  - Undated, 138646
    - Herbert Abrons Interview, No. 1, 60 min, 1990s undated, cuid3585; 134452 (Box 12, Object 11)
    - Herbert Abrons Interview, No. 2, 30 min, 1990s undated, cuid3586; 134519 (Box 12, Object 12)
    - Herbert Abrons Interview, No. 3, 1990s undated, cuid3587; 134447 (Box 12, Object 13)
    - Rose and Lucy Tortorella interview, 1990s undated, cuid3588; 134481 (Box 12, Object 14)
      It can be assumed that this oral history interview draws relation to the 1990 Public History Workshop, which explored the interactions between Chinese and Italian immigrants on the Lower East Side.
    - Rose and Lucy Tortorella interview, copy, 1990s undated, 1993; cuid3589; 134497 (Box 12, Object 15)
      There was a note attached to this cassette that reads: 'Henry Street Workshop,' which leads one to believe that this interview was conducted for the 1993 Public History Workshop that focused on the Henry Street Settlement House. There was, however, no date on the actual cassette.
    - Tony D'Apolito interview, copy, Tape #1 of 2, 1990s undated, cuid3590; 134457 (Box 12, Object 16)
    - Tony D'Apolito interview, copy, Tape #2 of 2, 1990s undated, cuid3591; 134458 (Box 12, Object 17)
    - Beethoven #1, #2, Tony D'Apolito, 1990s undated, cuid3592; 134474 (Box 12, Object 18)
      TDK MC90 Audio Cassette
    - Beethoven #3, Tony D'Apolito, 1990s undated, cuid3593; 134476 (Box 12, Object 19)
      TDK Maverick MC90, Audio Cassette
    - Vita Poliseno Interview, 1990s undated, cuid3594; 134509 (Box 12, Object 20)
      Scotch BX60-90 Audio Cassette
    - Vita Poliseno interview, copy, Side A only, 1990s undated, cuid3595; 134453 (Box 12, Object 21)
    - Anthony Rinaldi interview, 1990s undated, cuid3596; 134482 (Box 12, Object 22)
      There is good basis to assume that this oral history interview is related to the Public History Workshop of 1990, focusing on relations between Chinese and Italian immigrants on the Lower East Side.
    - Victoria Mascato interview, 1990s undated, cuid3597; 134485 (Box 12, Object 23)
      It can be assumed that this oral history interview related to the 1990 Public History Workshop, which focused on relations between Chinese and Italian immigrants on the Lower East Side.
    - Victoria Mascato interview, Copy, Side A only, 1990s undated, cuid3598; 134472 (Box 12, Object 24)
    - Stonecutters Riot in Washington Square, 1834, cuid3599; 134468 (Box 12, Object 25)
      Contents description and attached note
      This cassette contains a documentary created by associates of the Public History program. The topic of the documentary is the Stonecutters Riot in Washington Square, 1834. The label on the case notes that 'Rich, Eileen, Joan, Rachel, and Danny' were its producers.
    - Master Edit 1, Part 1, 1990s undated, cuid3600; 122591 (Box 13, Object 1)
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227312-1
    - Master Edit 1, Part 2, 1990s undated, cuid3601; 122592 (Box 13, Object 2)
    - Ports Interview excerpts, 1990s undated, cuid3602; 122597 (Box 13, Object 3)
    - J.A. Visuals #1, 1990s undated, cuid3603; 122593 (Box 13, Object 4)
    - Master Copy #1, Liz Sevcenko, 1990s undated, cuid3604; 122603 (Box 13, Object 5)
      Tape is blank, when played. There is no picture and no sound. Playing the tape produced a high-pitched noise from the equipment.
    - Master Copy #2, Liz Sevcenko, 1990s undated, cuid3605; 122571 (Box 13, Object 6)
      This tape, when played, appears to be an incomplete copy of the following item in this box ('Master Edit')
    - 'March of Time,' by Karen Y. Rosen, Part 1 of 1, 1990s undated, cuid3606; 122655; The duration of this cassette is 8 minutes. (Box 13, Object 7)
      Student work
      This documentary was created by student Karen Rosen.
    - 'Horizons' and 'Evening News,' Pamela Nelson Application, 1990s undated, cuid3607; 122660 (Box 13, Object 8)
    - Public History 3, Rich slideshow, 1990s undated, cuid3608; 122647 (Box 13, Object 9)
      Tape Characteristics
      The first quarter of this cassette appears blank when played in the proper equipment.
    - Unknown Public History tape, 1990s undated, cuid3609; 134435 (Box 13, Object 10)
    - Tape 2, begins with Charmaine, then J. Pento, 1990s undated, cuid3610; 134454 (Box 13, Object 11)
      Hi-8 Metal-P Video Cassette
    - Tape 1/Tape 3, 1990s undated, cuid3611; 134443 (Box 13, Object 12)
      Mislabeling of tape
      The case of this tape is labeled 'Tape 1,' but the tape itself is labeled 'Tape 3.' There is little else to determine the contents of the cassette.
      Maxell Audio Cassette, LN-90
    - Rehearsal #3, Oral Presentations, 1990s undated, cuid3612; 134430 (Box 13, Object 13)
    - Workshop, Camera Tests, 1990s undated, cuid3613; 134449 (Box 13, Object 14)
    - Tape 3, J. Pento, 1990s undated, cuid3614; 134448 (Box 13, Object 15)
    - Tape 1, 1990s undated, cuid3615; 134444 (Box 13, Object 16)
      Sony, Hi-8 Metal-P Video Cassette
    - Tape 1, Practice Tape, 1990s undated, cuid3616; 134486 (Box 13, Object 17)
      Hi-8 Video Cassette, P6-30HMPX
    - 'Margaret Sanger: A Public Nuisance,' documentary, 1990s undated, cuid3617; 122628 (Box 13, Object 18)
    - '1968' Edits for Rachel Bernstein, 1990s undated, cuid3618; 122625 (Box 13, Object 19)
    - 'Americana' Video, Tape 3, 1990s undated, cuid3619; 122586 (Box 13, Object 20)
    - Tape 1, Juan Mendez Interview, 1990s undated, cuid3620; 122621 (Box 15, Object 10)
    - Copy, 1/31, 1990s undated, cuid3621; 138648 (Box 15, Object 11)
      Analog video cassette
    - Master Edit, 1990s undated, cuid3622; 122572 (Box 15, Object 12)
      Tape format
      Tape contents
      This tape contains footage from various sources, including the previous listing ('Master Copy #2').
    - 'Afrikamerica: A Strolling Slide Show,' documentary, 1990s undated, cuid3623; 122646 (Box 15, Object 13)
    - Public History slide show, 1990s undated, cuid3624; 138647 (Box 15, Object 14)
    - 'Harlem's Cotton Club,' Steve Bossous, undated, cuid3625; 170229 (Box 15, Object 15)
    - 'Union Square "Revitalized,"' Michael Shapiro, Public History, undated 2000s, cuid3626; 170230 (Box 15, Object 16)
    - 'Heaven Will Protect the Working Girl,' American Social History Film Library, undated, cuid3627; 170233 (Box 15, Object 17)
    - 'WPA Guide to NYC,' Mathilde Lerosier, undated, cuid3628; 170234 (Box 15, Object 18)
    - 'Building Public Housing in New York,' Tracy Neumann, undated, cuid3629; 170235 (Box 15, Object 19)
    - 'The Diamond District: Growing Pains,' Rebeccah Movsky, undated, cuid3630; 170236 (Box 15, Object 20)
    - 'City Kids Meet Ashcan Art,' Robert W. Snyder, undated, cuid3631; 170237 (Box 15, Object 21)
    - 'Beach Tunnel,' Terri Lonier, undated, cuid3632; 170238 (Box 15, Object 22)
    - 'Fulton Street Mall: Economics, Hop-Hop, and Ownership,' Jessika G. Drmacich, undated 2000s, cuid3633; 170240 (Box 15, Object 23)
      Two (2) DVD-R 8X
    - 'The Assimilation of a People: The Irish in New York,' Katern Murphy, Material Culture DVD, undated 2000s, cuid3634; 170241 (Box 15, Object 24)
      Apple DVD-R 8X
    - 'Women and the Univeristy in the 1920s...', Korean-American Exhibit at the Balch Institute, Pam Nelson, Microsoct Word-Macintosh, undated, cuid3635; 170244 (Box 15, Object 25)
      3M 3.5" Diskette
    - 'MSHome.JPG,' 1. Michael Shapiro, Public History, 2. Sarah Nolan Window, undated, cuid3636; 170245 (Box 15, Object 26)
      IBM 3.5" Diskette
    - 'Public History Scanned Papers: NYU Workshop, Sporn, Nelson, Barnett, Mart...", undated, cuid3637; 170246 (Box 15, Object 27)
    - 'Becoming and American in Easy Installments: Material Culture and Consumerism on New York's Lower East Side 1900-1940,' Molly Mitchell, MSWord and Wordperfect files, undated, cuid3638; 170247 (Box 15, Object 28)
      Verbatim DataLife MF 2HD 3.5" Diskette
    - Jonathan Kovel, Director of Photography undated, cuid3639; 170787 (Box 18, Object 1)
    - Lawrence Weschler, Tape A, undated, cuid3640; 170788 (Box 18, Object 2)
    - Lawrence Weschler, Tape B, undated, cuid3641; 170789 (Box 18, Object 3)